aynax.com 2017-02-20

# Privacy Policy :: Aynax.com

Aynax.com owns and operates this online invoicing application. Aynax.com is committed to keep the information of our customers safe. This privacy policy discusses the use of and disclosure of the information that we collect from you, as a part of routine operations of the application. By visiting and registering at Aynax.com, you consent and authorize us to collect and use your personal information as per this document as well as the Terms of Service. Aynax.com reserves the right to update and modify this Privacy Policies whenever it becomes necessary. 

Collection of Information    
Aynax.com collects the personal information, voluntarily provided by you, when you order/request information for services at Aynax.com. This information can include your names, physical addresses, email addresses, company names, designation, and other relevant information. Customers who subscribe to the paid account at Aynax.com do so via Paypal. Consequently, their credit card details are collected on Paypal's website (their privacy policy can be found [here](https://www.paypal.com/us/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside)). 

Use of Cookies    
When you navigate through and use Aynax.com, we may store some bits of information onto your computer. These bits of information are usually in the form of small text files 'cookies'. Cookies are not computer programs but rather simple pieces of data that ensures we are able to operate the site. Cookies allow us to record the traffic on our website, your preferences, and help us offer you specific features when you login and use the application. 

Use of Personal Information    
Maintaining your personal information helps us improve our services and communicate to you regarding your services requested, your bill, and any other necessary information/update. Aynax.com holds your privacy at utmost importance. We take full measures to ensure that there is no loss, alteration or misuse of your personal information. Hence, we do not share, rent or disclose this information to any other person except our employees, which is a prerequisite to provide you exhaustive support and services. All information is password protected, ensuring that it is only accessed by employees/representatives involved in providing you support. 

Updating your Personal Information    
If you are an account holder or subscriber, you can update your personal as well as company information via logging into the application and updating the settings. 

Contacting us regarding Privacy Policy    
If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, you can mail us at support@aynax.com, write us at PO Box 628, West Chester, PA 19381, or call 646-664-1014.
